Guide to the Henri Chopin Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Material, 1957-2007; Series VII; 15.62; (46 boxes) + 3 objects
  - Sound Recordings
    - Audiocassettes, commercially released and non-commercial
      - Chopin, Henri. "Poesie Sonore" (CAS 5), undated; 1; 01:08:40; Static and a high amount of buzz can be heard on the tape. Clicks and pops can also be heard. The program is distorted at times. (Box 63, Item barcode 39002104502985)
        Emissions 9 et 10
      - Dana, Llys. "Songs 1,2" (CAS 18), undated; 1; 00:22:01; The program is distorted at times. (Box 63, Item barcode 39002104502993)
      - Duke, Walwicz, and Zurbrugg. "Sound Poetry" (CAS 21), 1987 February; 1; 00:30:55 (Box 63, Item barcode 39002104503009)
      - Machine for Making Sense. "On Second Thoughts" (CAS 6), 1993; 1; 00:50:05 (Box 63, Item barcode 39002104503017)
      - Pi.O. "Pi.O. Sound Poetry" (CAS 7), undated; 1; 00:18:40; Buzz can be heard on the tape. (Box 63, Item barcode 39002104503025)
      - Pissier, Ph. "Mi-Ange, Mi-Demon" (CAS 8), undated; 1; 00:42:49 (Box 63, Item barcode 39002104503033)
        Philippe Pissier (85-86); en et mis en voix par Jéan-pierre Espil (87)
      - Radio Bourges. "Les Poemes" (CAS 16), undated; 1; 00:49:34; Static can be heard. Audio in the left channel was recorded at a lower volume on the tape. (Box 64, Item barcode 39002104503165)
        Apollinaile G O 11; Seuphor; Pansaers; Neuhuys; PAB; H.C. Arp.; Theo van Does.; Picalia
      - Sarenco. "Sarenco Anthology" (CAS 9), 1978-1979; 1; 01:32:12; The program is distorted at times. Audio is silent on the left channel from 1:22:23-1:29:41. (Box 64, Item barcode 39002104503173)
        Side 1/Side 2
        "Accumulaliou"/L'Azmaniana" (Homage to Armian), 1979
        "C'est [Vzai] De Vree", 1979
        "Yo ablo", 1978
        "Barb (a) ra", 1978
        "Sono un poeta", 1978
        "Concerto in 1a minore", 1978
        "Piéa Fausse", 1979
        "Cosu resta", 1978
        "Peom 12. 78", 1978
        "Music 78"
        "Trinidad", 1979
        "La balalaika", 1979
        "Desiderio", 1979
        "Die Zauberflöte", 1978
      - "New Sounds Gallery" (CAS 10), 1984 October 30 & 31; 1; 00:45:10; The program is distorted at times. (Box 64, Item barcode 39002104503181)
        CFRO-FM; Vancouver
      - "Poesie pour Rire, Poesie Sonore" (CAS 11), 1991 April-May; 1; 01:14:10; Static can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. (Box 64, Item barcode 39002104503199)
      - RP "Chopin" (CAS 12) 1 of 2, 1982 September 3; 1; 01:03:11; The program is distorted at times. (Box 64, Item barcode 39002104503207)
      - RP "Chopin" (CAS 13) 2 of 2, 1982 September 3; 1; 00:25:18 (Box 64, Item barcode 39002104503215)
      - A. C. R. De A a Z de H. Chopin et P. Zumthor (CAS 14) 1 of 2, 1992 May 31; 1; 01:37:09 (Box 64, Item barcode 39002104503223)
      - A. C. R. De A a Z de H. Chopin et P. Zumthor (CAS 15) 2 of 2, 1992 May 31; 1; 00:22:52 (Box 64, Item barcode 39002104503231)
      - Subtile Voice by C. W. de H. C. (CAS 20), 1985 April; 1; 00:10:20; The program is distorted at times. (Box 64, Item barcode 39002104503249)
        San Jose, CA
        1) Subtile Voice, 6'17"
        2) Round Destruction for a poem, 4'
      - Unidentified, undated; 1; 00:00:29 (Box 64, Item barcode 39002104503256)
      - Unidentified, undated; 1; 00:17:23 (Box 64, Item barcode 39002104503264)
      - Works by Chopin, unsorted, (15 audiocassettes)
        - Pira, Marc. 3 études de mécanique sonore naturelle, undated; 1; 00:34:06 (Box 65, Item barcode 39002109889973)
          Face A: Petite cuisine concrète; Face B: Vent faible à modéré * Aquaphonie nº 1
        - Bernstein, Buck, la Palma, Piombino, Wendt and Zweig. Lobby Newsletter 18/19, 1982-1983; 1; 00:58:04; Static can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. (Box 65, Item barcode 39002109889981)
          There is a list of contents included with the audiocassette.
          Side 1: Paul Buck
          Seduction in Cars (4.10)
          The Bleed Stocking in Thigh (4.50)
          (extracts from) Journies to the Perpendicular (8.15)
          Nick Piombino - Phase (3.00)
          Untitled (2.54)
          Untitled (1.52)
          Untitled (1.31)
          As in Me (2.11)
          Side 2:
          Charles Bernstein - Islets/Irritations Azoot D'Puund (6.43 and 3.44)
          Marina la Palma - Ixiva Portal Exo (3.48)
          Ellen Zweig - Green Silk (6.48)
          Larry Wedt - What is Man? (8.10)
        - Media - Space, 1982 March 14; 1; 00:28:01; The program is distorted at times. (Box 65, Item barcode 39002109889999)
          A list of contents include:
          poor australia
          grand america
          be right
          confrontation
          i don't wanu
          disappearing
          perth
        - Schwerner, Armand and Velez, Glen. New Wilderness Summer Solstice, 1984-06-19; 1; 00:28:42 (Box 65, Item barcode 39002109890005)
          at 8BC
        - Vonna-Michell, e.e. and Fisher, Allen. Chest Breath & Car Wash Interview, 1978 summer; 1; 00:19:52; The program is distorted at times. (Box 65, Item barcode 39002104502589)
        - Eclatement & Limitation - Taliesin, 1980; 1 (Box 65, Item barcode 39002104502597)
          Songs listed on the audiocassette are as follows:
          intrigues
          solitude
          les dames de la cour au palais du roy
          l'homme noble
          jour et nuit
          loyauté
        - Heinrich, Michael. Lyrics, 1992 December; 1; 00:15:46 (Box 65, Item barcode 39002104502605)
        - Sauvagnac, Nicole. (Théatre de l'Immédiat), 1982; 1; 00:37:11; High frequency background noise can be heard on the tape. (Box 65, Item barcode 39002104502621)
          Sculpter la parole du vent. 1/Discussion aquatique; 2/Etude sur le vent.
        - Sauvagnac, Nicole. (Théátre de I'Immédiat), 1982; 1; 00:36:36 (Box 65, Item barcode 39002104502639)
          Sculpter la parole du vent. 1. Discussion aquatique, 2. Etude sur le vent; Dolby B, stereo
        - Vizents, A., Khakrabarty, Amanda. Media-Space Genetics, 1983 June; 1; 00:21:24; The program is distorted at times. (Box 65, Item barcode 39002104502647)
        - Le sonosaure/Le livre sonore, 1967; 1; 01:27:12 (Box 65, Item barcode 39002104502654)
          The contents of the audiocassette are listed as follows:
          Kinkao (14'22")
          Petites orgues (7'28")
          Tribal (7'28")
          Machine (10')
          Maounishnou (5')
          Queiques formules utiles (6'34")
          Au-delà des machines (7'14")
          S'abolir sonore (14'30")
          Eha! (7'12")
          La mort d'Antonin Artaud (8')
          Rire construit (4'50")
        - Heinrich, Michael. Lyrics, 1992 December; 1; 00:15:50 (Box 65, Item barcode 39002104502662)
        - Espace Effondrement Les Yeux Fermés, 1986?; 1; 00:29:47; Static can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. (Box 65, Item barcode 39002104502670)
        - Das Synthetische Mischgewebe. La Boîte de Doolittle part I, II, III, 1989 February; 1; 00:49:57; The program is distorted at times. (Box 65, Item barcode 39002104502860)
          Voices and sounds of animals, recorded by various institutions around the world. Produced in a 8-track studio with snakes, pigs, orcas, fishes, insects, bats, penguins, birds, shacals, leopards...
        - Mac Low, Jackson. New Wilderness Audiographics, 1977; 1; 00:57:33; The program is distorted at times. A high amount of buzz can be heard. (Box 65, Item barcode 39002104502878)
      - Works by Chopin, unsorted, (35 audiocassettes)
        - Kostelanetz, Richard. Audio Art, 1980; 1; 00:46:22; Audio is muffled at times. There is a high amount of hiss on the tape. (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503629)
          Stereo. This audiocassette includes: "This is My Poem", "Plateaux", "Alphabet", "Praying to the Lord", "Foreshortenings", "Counting", "Declaration of Independence", "Excelsior", "Richard Kostelanetz, plus commentary.
        - Kucharz. Canal St. (City Street Scenes I), undated; 1; 00:16:22; A high amount of hiss and background noise can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503637)
        - Thomas, Martin. Home Front Manhattan: An Acoustic Essay on Homelessness and the Gulf War, undated; 1; 00:58:53 (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503645)
        - Pont, Gèrard. "A François Dupiêre", 1983 March; 1; 00:06:01 (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503652)
        - Untitled, undated; 1; This cassette is blank. It has not been digitized. (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503660)
        - Buck, Paul and Parant, Jean-Luc. Reading xxxx7/Tik, undated; 1; 01:08:06; Static can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503678)
        - Miccini, Eugenio. Il Soma, Le Soma, El Soma, 1978-1991; 1; 00:23:14 (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503686)
          Other contents listed on the audiocassette include: Della Probità Dell' Informal/One (1991) and Alfabeto (1978)
        - Diede[?], Yau[?], Shrei/Aux Levres Du Nid, Le Silence, 1973 and 1984; 1; 00:42:19; The audio is silent from 9:38-10:17. (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503694)
        - Loiseau, Pierre. Poévie, 1993 March 11; 1; 01:31:46; The program is distorted at times. (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503702)
        - Rebotier, Jacques. "Poésie sur Parole", undated; 1; 00:43:47 (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503710)
        - Rebotier, Jacques. "Poésie sur Parole", undated; 1; 00:28:00 (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503728)
        - Amirkhanian, Charles. New Works 1981-1982, 1983 May 30; 1; 00:43:03 (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503736)
          A handwritten liner note reads: Souvenir of San Francisco for Henri Chopin with best wishes! Charles Mirkhanian.
          1. "Dog of Stravinsky"
          2. "Hypothetical Moments"
          3. "Maroa"
          4. "History of Collage"
          5. "Church Car II"
          1. "The Putts"
          2. "Pastor"
          3. "Andas"
          4. "Dot Bunch"
        - Chopin, Henri and Vonna-Michell, Erik. To Ray the Rays, 1985 August 21; 1; 00:09:57; The program is distorted at times. (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503744)
        - Minarelli, Enzo. Untitled, 1984 August 30; 1; 01:26:26; The program is distorted at times. (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503751)
          A handwritten message on the audiocassette's liner notes reads: For Henri Chopin, Enzo Minarelli, 1984-08-30. The contents of the audiocassette are listed below.
          Kandinsky; 3'10", 1979
          Chorus; 4'10", 1983
          Rapsodissea; 12'55", 1983
          Wow Flutter Stop; 6'45", 1983
          Res Tauro; a. fermatura; 5'20", b. protezione; 6'20", c. foderatura; 7'20", 1983
          Fisch ìo; 3'53", 1984
          Echair; 2'40", 1984
          Urloh!; 3'45", 1984
          Anacoluto; 2'50", 1984
          Rebut-Rebus; 3'25", 1984
          Accenti; 2'00", 1984
          A-Voce; 35", 1984
          Geosound-Geosonica; 4'25", 1984
          Con Sonanti; 4'35", 1984
          Miss-Mix; 2'50", 1984
          Labirinto; 8'40", 1984
        - Geerken, Hartmut. Untitled, 1989 and 1990; 1; 01:32:21 (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503769)
        - Blank, J. Learning the Scales, 1985 January 1; 1; 00:10:53; A high amount of hiss can be heard on the tape. (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503777)
          A handwritten note on the audiocassette reads: To Henri with love.
        - Schenh'au[?], Valeri. Sense - non - sense, 1993; 1; 00:31:38; The program is distorted at times. (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503785)
          Pour Henri Chopin avec meilleutes salusations; Berlin, Studio Rudbert Music
        - B.V., undated; 1; 00:28:06 (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503793)
        - Rarabet, René, undated; 1; 00:32:28 (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503801)
        - Schwerner and Stein. So Po Festival, 1980 April 13; 1; 00:19:17 (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503819)
          A note included with the audiocassette reads: To England.
        - Charbonnier. Untitled, undated; 1; 01:30:29; The program is distorted at times. High background noise can be heard on the tape. (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503827)
        - Radio Bou[?] H. C., undated; 1; 00:40:52; Static can be heard on the tape. (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503835)
        - Marlow, Jack. Song for Voices, undated; 1; 00:24:11 (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503843)
        - Kraft, P. Marine, undated; 1; 00:14:47 (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503850)
        - Les Niches Heures de L'alphabet, undated; 1; 00:25:08; A high amount of buzz can be heard on the tape. (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503868)
        - V.M., Erik. To Henri, undated; 1; 00:34:33; Static can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503876)
        - Deuis chaus ou, undated; 1; 00:25:46; The program is distorted at times. A high amount of hiss and static can be heard on the tape. (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503884)
        - Higgins. Bodies Electric: Arches, undated; 1; 00:22:22 (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503892)
        - Chopin, Henri. Poesie Sonore/Emissions 5 et 6, undated; 1; 01:10:00; The program is distorted at times. (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503926)
          Emission 5, 37'
        - Chopin, Henri. Poesie Sonore/ Emissions 7 et 8, undated; 1; 01:17:34; Static can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503900)
          Emission 7, 30'; Emission 8, 35'
        - Chopin, Henri. Poesie Sonore/Emissions 11 et 12, undated; 1; 01:14:53; Static can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503918)
          Emission 11, 35'
        - Smith, Hazel and Dean, Roger. Serpent ex Spearhead, undated; 1; 00:08:05 (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503934)
          Contents on the audiocassette include: Signed Original and Simultaneity.
        - Manfredini, Federica. Half Drowning, undated; 1; 00:35:09; A high amount of hiss and static can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. Audio in the left channel is recorded at a very low level throughout the first 35 minutes of the program. (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503942)
          A list of contents are included with the audiocassette.
          1. Half Drowning (3 movimenti), 6'
          2. Wasser War, 4'
          3. Dove Vado, 1' 40"
          4. Phoney, 6'
          5. My 5 Notes, 5'
          6. Frequenza, 7'
          7. See the Sea, 3' 30"
          8. Exchanges 2, 56"
          9. To Be or Not to Be, 1' 32"
        - Chopin, Henri. A C R 2, 1987 March 22; 1; 01:00:36; Static can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. The program is recorded at a very high level. (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503959)
        - Les Dossiers D'Espace 2: Poesie Sonore --1--, 1992 March 10; 1; 01:00:47; A high amount of hiss can be heard on the tape. (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503967)
      - Works by others, unsorted, (34 audiocassettes)
        - Festival d'In(ter)ventions I: Neoson(g) Cabaret, 1985; 1; 00:56:22 (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506317)
          Face A / Face B
          1. The Woeurks, 4:52
          2. Okarina, 3:41
          3. Même la Technologie Fragmente, 5:25
          4. News, 4:25
          5. Glass Lass, 2:54
          6. (Je n'ai goút à rien), 2:33
          7. Sphère Sonore, 5:09
          1. Kipchogue Keino, 5:39
          2. Bestiaire Urbain et Autres Civiltés Bizarres, 4:35
          3. Temps Réel, 1:04
          4. Quelques Formules Utiles, 6:34
          5. Sans Titre, 4:12
          6. Lecture Générale, 2:59
        - Bang Crash Wallopp (Book 2), May 13; 1; 01:02:48; The program is distorted at times. (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506325)
          Live Saturday the 13th of May at the LMC.
        - Chopin, Henri. Poesie Sonore, 1972; 1; 00:19:14 (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506333)
          The contents of this audiocassette are included.
          Side A
          1. Le Voyage Lablovelaire (August 1971), 11'42"
          2. Le Cri - Homage to Marcel Janco (September 1971), 7'08"
        - Wendt, Larry. New and Slightly Used Text-Sound Compositions, 1977; 1; 01:13:50; The program is distorted at times. (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506341)
        - Wendt, Larry. Metropolitan Fractalizations, 1978 November 25; 1; 00:55:01 (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506358)
        - Pisek, Bruno. Est Etiam in Dicendo Quidati Cantus Obscurior, undated; 1; 00:14:57; The program is distorted at times. (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506366)
        - Éclaboussurés Et Realites, 1987; 1; 00:39:13; The program is distorted at times. (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506374)
          Les Cygnes
          Tessynabe
          Sentiers Battus
          Rain At One O'clock
          Lee Dernier Train
          In Die Production
          Strang I
          D. Generation
          Forch
          Strang IV
          Turbulence
        - Chopin, Henri. Poesie Sonore Internationale, undated; 1; 00:57:02; The program is distorted at times. Audio on the left channel is silent from 17:06-17:27. (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506382)
          Seuphor, Michel. Tout en Roulant les RR
          Dufrêne, François. Les Joyeux Sisyphe II
          Heidsieck, Bernard. Démocratie
          Chopin, Henri. Le Parlement Européan
          de Vree, Paul. Magdalena, Appassionata, Lettervrouw
          Novak, Ladislav. Deux poèmes onomatopées
          Gysin, Brion. Junk is no good baby
          Mon, Franz. Ja-Nein-Parabel
          Rühm, Gerhard. Spricht 'über' Auditive Poesie
          Jandl, Ernst. Vom Lautgedicht
          Lora-Totino, Arrigo. 'Smoke Words' for H. Chopin
          Giorno, John. Raspberry
          Hanson, Sten. The Glorious Desertion
        - Dufrêne, François. Cantate des mots camés, 1971-1977; 1; 00:44:53 (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506390)
        - Micoski, Claude. Anthologie sonore de Poésie, 1989; 1; 00:29:52 (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506408)
        - Polipoesia Primera Antologia, undated; 1; 01:04:58 (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506416)
        - Mann, Chris. doin 2s, undated; 1; There is deterioration to parts of this audiocassette (sticky shed syndrome). The tape has not been digitized. (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506424)
        - Boeswillwald, P. Fous de Révolution, 1989; 1; 00:13:32 (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506432)
          overture Danton
        - In die Irre gent alles, 1992 November 19; 1; 01:34:37 (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506440)
        - Sampler Cassette, 1977; 1; 00:51:10 (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506457)
          Side 1 / Side 2
          Rothenberg, Jerome. Singing his total translation of the 12th of the 17 "Horse Songs" in the blessingway of Frank Mitchell
          Excerpt from "March 1974" of Hannah Weiner's "Clairvoyant Journal"
          Schwerner, Armand. Translation of Sophocles' "Philoctetes"
          Holst, Spencer. "The Frog"
          Corner, Philip and Fontana, William. "Metal Meditations with Fontana"
          Mac Low, Jackson. Excerpt from "Homage to Leona Bleiweiss"
          Lockwood, Annea. "World Rhythms"
          Crow Dog, Leonard and Mary. Traditional Sioux Peyote Songs
          Schechner, Richard and McIntosh, Joan. A field recording of bamoo jew's harp music
          Morrow, Charlie. "Evening Star Chant"
        - Seuphor, Michel. Quelque 60 du XXº siècle, 1990; 1; 00:42:50 (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506465)
          Face 1 / Face 2
          Poème Modèle, 1926
          Poème 131, 1927
          Poème 132, 1927
          Sardaigne, 1926
          Poème 110, 1927
          Poème 111, 1927
          Tout en roulant les RR, 1927
          Sinnge sange, 1929
          Erreur Brevetée, 1929
          Cartes sur table, 1963
          Discours Politique, 1952
          Chant Toltèque, 1963
          Langue vivante, 1963
          Maille hillilil, 1962
          Chanson de la dernière chance, 1966
          Chanson porte-chance, 1966
          Pour la St Erasme, 1978
          Pour la St Oiseau, 1978
          Falamagre, 1963
          Chanson de la fatalité, 1966
          Pour la St Socrate, 1978
          Pour la St Spinoza, 1978
          Le nageur, 1960
          Comme le temps passe, 1962
          Les vieux amis, 1963
          Le Rossignol, 1964
          Fifèle à l'amour du jeu, 1973
          La Puste, 1972
          Investiture, 1973
          Un résumé de tout, 1973
          Communiqué, 1958
          Servir la Poésie, 1958
          Le nouveau-né, 1962
          Curriculum, 1972
          Lentement, 1960
          Prière sur l'Acropole, 1962
        - Flynt, Henry. "You Are My Everlovin' " / "Celestial Power", 1980 and 1981; 1; 01:28:11; The program is distorted at times. (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506473)
        - Chinea, Mark. Hammersley, Richard. Radin, Nick. Tabor, Richard and Bekerian, Debra. The 4 Day Opportunity, 1981; 1; 00:58:43; The program is distorted at times. (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506481)
          This is a performance from an arts festival at Reading University: 1979-06-28.
          view data
          alt sx
          Xpls x
          a contralaboration
          A Theory of Danoing
          a little sleepy
          some humus
          W - -
          Minimal Studies 2
          in working
          Room Studies Volume 1
          Cloud Chamber
          loam
        - Hudak, John. momentumless identity, undated; 1; 01:01:58 (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506499)
          "many sparrows"
          "the lost pleasures"
        - Owen Sound. Underwhich Audiographic Series, "Beyond the Range", 1980 September; 1; 01:18:27 (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506507)
        - Nitsch, Hermann. Orgelkonzert, 1986 December 9; 1; 01:03:18 (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506515)
        - Paté de Voix, 1985; 1; 01:01:18; The program is distorted at times. (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506523)
          torino, giugno
          Side A / Side B
          1. Porta, P.
          2. Colonna, G.
          3. Sproccati, S.
          4. Arbizzani, L.
          5. Bertola, C.
          6. Xerra, W.
          7. Tramutoli, G.
          8. Collo, R.
          1. Totino, A. L.
          2. Trentini, R.
          3. Cena, S.
          4. Giachino, L.
          5. Olmeda, P.
          6. Henrard, A.
          7. Vitacchio, A.
          8. Gherini, A.
          9. Carollo, A.
          10. Servetti, M.
        - Wendt, Larry. World-Class Technology / Frog Hollow, San Jose, undated; 1; 00:53:59; The program is distorted at times. (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506531)
          1. San Jose Holiday, 9' 36"
          2. Broken Crystals, 11' 41"
          3. A Word Processing, 6' 39"
          1. Painted Rocks, 11' 49"
          2. Reaqanomics, 4' 34"
          3. Zolmak the Zygon, 9' 5"
        - Bertozzi. Fogli e acque, 1992; 1; 00:03:08; Levels in audio varies throughout the first minute and a half of programming. (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506549)
        - Prism International, 1990; 1; 00:56:42 (Box 67, Item barcode 39002104506556)
          Clark, Theresa and Wilson, Carletta. "Shadows"
          Clark, Theresa and Wilson, Carletta. "Naked with Thorns"
          Clark, Theresa and Wilson, Carletta. "This Light Called Darkness"
          Attila the Stockbroker. "Contributory Negligence"
          Attila the Stockbroker. "Death in Bromley"
          Attila the Stockbroker. "A Bang and A Wimpy"
          Attila the Stockbroker. "Libyan Students from Hell"
          Courtemanche, Peter. Excerpt from "Radio Journal"
          MacLeod, Scott. Excerpts from "The Drunken Jungle
          Skratz, G. P. and Davis, Bob. Excerpts from "Mass of the Scattered Almonds"
          McCaffery, Steve. "Anticollabora"
          McCaffery, Steve. "Childe Harold's Phonemage"
          Bakken, Dick. "Ya Hi Yu Niva
          Bakken, Dick. "How to Eat Corn"
          Bakken, Dick. "Om Raksha"